[music]
[музыка]
2,000 rubles for such an apartment is a lot I
2.000 руб за такую квартиру это много В
mean, am I laughing?
смысле смеюсь что ли Мебель Дубовая
Oak furniture, show me what kind of oak it is. It's chipboard, you can see it's chipboard with just a coating like oak. Why would I lie, oh my god, autonomous heating. Oak furniture. What are
автономное отопление Дубовая мебель Ну
you doing? Knock. Well, if there's a knock.  will be like
ты что постучи Ну если стук будет как
oak or
дуб или
chipboard Well, the ringing sound is not oak in oak
ДСП Ну Звонкий звук это не дуб у дуба
I am furniture I am engaged in furniture in oak there is a
я мебелью Я занимаюсь мебелью у дуба
dull sound it is dense
глухой звук он плотность
Hello,
Здравствуйте Вы
where are you from Volgograd Volgograd I understood
откуда Волгоград Волгоград понял С вами
Everything is
всё
fine with you, generally excellent And I understood somehow a
нормально вообще отлично А понял как-то
little strange it looks like
немножко странно выглядит вроде как
Well, I  I did my hair like this especially for laughs
Ну я специально для смеха вот так волосы
I'm not talking about hair
сделал Я не про волосы я
at all What's the big deal Well, it seems For
вообще А что вообще что Ну походу Для
laughs Everything is somehow For laughs Well, okay, that's
смеха Всё как-то Для смеха Ну ладно это
it Okay And what are you talking about
такое Окей А чём общаетесь
here I've been a philosopher since childhood on any topic I'm
тут я философ с детства на любую тему Я
also a
тоже
philosopher You, by the way,
философ Вы
are by vocation  I am also a
кста по призванию Я тоже по призванию
philosopher by vocation. To what movement do you
философ вы к какому течению себя
belong? I mean, the
относите как В смысле течению
Orthodox movement. Well, to what movement of
православный Ну к какому течению
philosophy? I understand that the Orthodox movement is
философии Я понимаю что православный к
philosophical movement of some kind
философскому течению какому
and not to my own I understood well
а нет к собственному понял ну там
let's do it this way materialism
давайте так материализм
idealism
идеализм
realism That is you think that being
реализм То есть вы считаете что бытиё
prevails over
превалирует над
consciousness I definitely understood And how do you
сознанием однозначно понял А как вы
feel about the
относитесь к
corpuscular-wave dualism of
корпускулярно-волнового дуализм
Light not This is something I'm missing here I'm not
Света не Это я что-то мимо тут я не
literate Well what What  for example, light
грамот Ну что Что например э свет себя
behaves both as matter and as a
ведёт и как материя и как
wave Well, this is more related to astronomy than to
волна Ну это скорее к астрономии чем к
philosophy What does it relate to astronomy
философии относится к чему к астрономии
than to philosophy Astronomy
чем к философии относится астрономии -
is
это
physics Well, physics is connected there
физика Ну физика она там связана
Astronomers are all connected I
астрономи всё совсем связано
understand, it's interesting, that is, you are a representative of the
понял интересно то есть Вы представитель
Genetic school  that everything is connected to everything
генов ской школы что всё со всем связано
but everything can be
но всё можно
untied I didn't say that I am a
развязать Я не говорил что я по
philosopher by education I honestly say
образованию философ я честно сказать
Diogenes or Diogenes A yes What
диогена ли именно диогена А да Какой
Diogenes I only know about him that he
диогена я про него знаю только то что он
limited himself in everything there is something
себя ограничивал во всём там чтото
pi from the
пи из
palm Well, like nothing
ладошки Ну что типа ничего не
Alexander the Great needs to be done what can I
надо и Александр Македонский подол что
do for you he
для тебя сделать он
says Understand how do you feel about
говорит Поня как относитесь к тому что
Putin attacking
Путин напал на
Ukraine
Украину
Well, not really Everything is cash on Ukraine, they
Ну там не совсем Всё пун нал на Укра
share big
делят большие
money that we have  you have never seen
бабки которых мы с вами не видали
and most likely will not see
никогда и скорее всего не увидим
and all this is in
вот и это всё в
such Well, it's just popular to discuss it
таком Ну просто народно так это обсудить
Well, it's
Ну это
funny and what kind of
смешно а какие
grannies I don't know what kind we are I
бабки я не знаю какие каких мы с вами я
say we
говорю не
have not seen But you can tell me look
видели А вот можете рассказать смотрите
I live in Lithuania in the city  kaunos
Я живу в Литве в городе каунос Да как
How is it that our little Lithuania
так получается что Наша маленькая Литва
lives better than Russia which has
живёт лучше чем Россия у которой есть
oil gas
нефть газ
diamonds What's better I I
алмазы Что лучше я я
look I look minimum
смотрю я смотрю минимальный уровень
wage average median they are all higher
зарплаты средний медианный они все выше
than in Russia no There is also such
чем в России нет Там есть же ещё и такая
crap as this well How much are you  you spend no
фигня как это ну Сколько ты тратишь
matter what I spend I have more left
ско бы я не тратил у меня остатся больше
than a Russian gets in general well I don't
чем россиянин получает вообще ну я не
want to argue with you I'm not an economist
хочу с вами спорить я не экономист
but again you never know who has it first of
но опять же мало ли у кого как во-первых
all
таки
but one thing is there income for example 1000
и одно дело там доход например там 1000
euros Well
евро Ну
figuratively but it goes away  so I
образно но уходит вот я
left with a friend, I have a German from the Volga region,
с товарищем уехал у меня немец поволжью
by the way, his last, excuse my French,
кстати его посл извините мой французский
well, we corresponded for about 20 years and in the
Ну лет 20 переписывались и в конце
end, either they were being followed or something, in
концов то ли за ними следят то ли что
short, I got angry with him,
короче я на него рассердился
and he has expenses, he remains
вот а у него по траты у него остаётся
there  something in hand there something 200 euros
там что-то на руках там что-то 200 евро
What
Что
Well for now he's paying for the apartment for this For that for
Ну пока он за квартиру за то За сё за
gasoline and he's short with
бензин и он короче с
his head
голо
And maybe we pay
А у нас может быть может быть платит
less
меньше
But Well here I am sitting in the
Но Ну вот я сижу в
apartment 2,000 rubles I pay for it  per
квартире 2.000 руб Я за неё плачу в
month Well, so much apartment 2,000
месяц Ну так много квартиру 2.000
rubles how how
руб как как
2,000 rubles for such an apartment is a lot
2000 руб за такую квартиру это много В
I mean, what furniture Oak show me what
смысле сме что мебе Дубовая покажи какая
oak It's chipboard
дубовая Это ДСП у
you can see chipboard with just a coating like
тебя видно ДСП с просто покрытием таким
oak Why would I lie to you, oh my God, autonomous
под дуб Зачем мне врать ё-моё автономное
heating Oak furniture Well, you  what
отопление Дубовая мебель Ну ты что
knock Well if the knock will be like oak or
постучи Ну если стук будет как дуб или
chipboard Well a ringing sound it is not oak oak is
ДСП Ну Звонкий звук это не дуб у дуба
deaf I am furniture I am engaged in furniture
Глухо я мебелью Я занимаюсь мебелью у
oak has a dull sound it is dense I
дуба глухой звук он плотность большая Я
do not want to swear quarrel nothing Oaks
не хочу ругаться ссориться ничего Дубов
are Belarusian I have been engaged in furniture for 18 years
это Белорусская я 18 лет занимаюсь
in 2 years will be twentieth  everything is
мебелью через 2 года будет двадцатом все
clearer in short this is Belarusian oak I
видней короче это это белорусский дуб я
don't know what it sounds like I can't Well
не знаю как что звучит я не могу Ну
there is no way to dispute whether the sound is like this or
никак оспаривать вообще звук такой или
not I generally  Glukhova I am not a musician
нет Я вообще Глухова я не музыкант
but considering
но с учётом
that my mother worked in this company The
что в этой фирме работала моя маменька
Kingdom of Heaven is
Царство небесное это
oak that is at least the facades that
дуб то есть по крайней мере фасады то
is inside the shelves of course will be made of sticks
есть внутри полки конечно будут из палок
as
как
usual Well I just mean that
обычно Ну я просто про то что
it is in the sense and not like that with the apartment with this
его в смысле а не так с квартирой с этой
You
Ты её так
poured it out right away Well, yes, it's a small
сразу изл Ну да это небольшая
one-room
однокомнатная
apartment 35, what's the metro 2000 a month,
квартира 35 что метро 2000 в месяц
in short,
короче вообще
Daro has its own heating, that is, its own hot
Даро своё отопление то есть своя горячая
water I don't know why I
вода Я не знаю почему
say it in Russian here I mean, do you
здесь сказать по-русски В смысле а вы
want to say that you also have a normal
хотите сказать что у вас ещё нормальная
bathroom with a toilet  do you have a
ванна с туалетом есть или у вас
shared bathroom
совместный санузел
well here it's shared but why is it in one
ну здесь совместный а зачем он в одно
room in the sense of shared That is
комнату в смысле совместный То есть у
you have a shared one that is someone is bathing and
вас совместный то есть кто-то купается а
at that moment no one can go to the
в этот момент никто не может сходить
toilet well this is an apartment for one
туалет ну это квартира под одного
person it's not a family one
человека заточена она не семейная понял
you understand  you live without
вы сами живёте без
your mother and I also have a second mother, a
мамы да и у меня причём есть ещё вторая
second mother, but yes No, my mother is already in
ещё мама вторая но да Нет мама уже на
heaven, an
небе
apartment, but it is also bigger, but there we also
квартира но и она больше но там тоже
share because it is a one-room apartment,
совместно потому что однокомнатная если
even if we live together  if with a family then the conditions will need to
даже вдвоём жить если с семьёй то нужно
be changed
будет менять
Well I can do it I worked for 12 years under ELTO
условия Ну я это умею я 12 лет при элтом
so for me it's not a
трудился то есть для меня это ну не
question Well in terms of I understand how it's
вопрос Ну в плане я понимаю как это
done Why call an apartment bad it's
делается Зачем обзывать квартиру это как
not worse How is
не хуже Как
it an apartment by our Lithuanian standards
т по нашим литовским меркам это квартира
Sorry  Well, for one person it is
Извините ну для одного человека это
always
всегда
possible, you can show Well, it seems to be
можно можете показать Ну Она походу
small there How much is the main room
маленькая там вот Сколько комната
KTU Well, by eye Well,
имеет КТУ Ну на глазок Ну метров
18 meters Well, that's
18 Ну это
35 with a total area of 35 18 it can't be
35 при общей площади 35 18 не может быть
a room what Well, show it it can't be
комната чему Ну покажите не может быть
with a total of 35 14 the maximum
при общей 35 14 максимум
will be  I've been doing furniture for 18 years now I
будет я ж мебелью занимаюсь уже 18 лет Я
understand I
понимаю я разные комнаты
've seen different rooms but for example I'd rather brag
видел а вот например я лучше похвастаюсь
about the rooms Look at this from me de
с комнатами Вот смотри это у меня де
fascists
фашистов
took away
отнял
that Marie
что Мари
Mada from RNI
Мада из рни
where they shot closely if he took out
где расстреляли пристально если он вывез
such Oh yeah, that's enough
тако Ой да хватит что ли
they shot an air force colonel who  he
расстреляли полковника авиации кто его
will shoot him
будет расстреливать
he will shoot
он он
the looters Well if he took him out of Germany
мародёров Ну если он вывез из Германии
during the war I mean him I mean to shoot the
во время войны смысле ему В смысле отпи
Germans means to get three wounds and
немцев значит получить три ранения и
nothing to take or what This is
ничего не взять что ли Вот это
called a muzzle then your grandfather was a looter
называется морд то твой дед мародёр был
Yes no looting is taking
Да нет мародёрство - это забирать
the dead And this is a Trophy no no looting
мёртвых А это Трофей нет нет мародёрство
from the dead from the living Yes if a soldier Yes
у мёртвых у живых Да если солдат Да
robs certain valuables this is
грабит определённые ценности это
looting No no looting from the
мародёрство Нет нет мародёрство с
dead when you take no
мёртвого когда берёшь нет
no well  I don't want to I carried I can argue in general
нет ну не хочу я нес Я вообще спорить
but I don't like looting this is with Well, my
умею но не люблю мародёрство это с Ну
grandfather was a looter my grandfather was a looter like the
дед был мародёр дед был мародёр как и
whole Soviet army yes
вся Советская армия да
they robbed the
грабили
poor poor Basota this Soviet yes
нищая нищая Басота вот эта Советская да
the poor yes they stole bicycles there
беднота да она велосипеды воровала туда
dragged everything that as now washing machines
тянула всё что как и сейчас стиралки
televisions toilets  Do you seriously believe in
телевизоры унитазы Ты серьёзно веришь в
toilet bowls?
унитаза что ли
Well, just imagine how much it
Да ну это ты прикинь сколько перевезти
costs to transport this shit-stained toilet bowl home.
это обосраный унитаз до дома стоит Ну
Well, for you, its
вот для вас это
cheaper to drink for the guys there. Whos paying in the front?
дешевле там пацанам Кто на передке
Well, at my age,
платит Ну вот в моём возрасте
who am I, I dont know the exact numbers. Well, look
кто я точные цифры не знаю Ну вот гляд
at mine.  gray-haired  head they are all majors
на мою седую башку они все там майоры
there
там
colonels what kind of
полковники какие
toilets do they have at home half an hour naturally they are the
унитазы у них дом пол ча натурально они
same age
Прим ровесники
and before the draft simply because they have
и раньше призыва просто потому что они
already been in hot spots for them it is
на горячих точках уже были для них это
like a
как
drug what kind of toilet is there their something there
наркотик какой там унитаз их там что-то
they are not a toilet in a toilet  you are somehow
они ка не не унитаз в унитазе вы как-то
wrong and not like that and no
неправильно и не так и не
one will not drag and he I mean this
никакой не потащит и у него В смысле это
and he will not let anyone drag and so as
и он и не даст никому тащить причём
not to disgrace himself he has a full house a
чтобы не позорится у него дом полный
cup he has a house a wife a business he
чаша у него есть и дом жена бизнес он
just like that is a turn of phrase
просто как вот есть оборот речь такой
Dogs of war he heard that there was a war he was there
Псы войны он услышал что война он там
everything was there Caucasus Mavka everything in the world there he
все там Кавказ мавка всё на свете там
went further they don't let him have fun here bang
прошёл дальше не дают кайфовать тут чпок
Ukraine he blew himself up all the
Украина он подорвался всё говорит
wife says Wait for me a little what kind of toilet are
жена Подожди меня немножко какой унитаз
you kidding they
ты угораешь
still give them money
дают всё
I don't even know Well, you can't
равно я даже не знаю Ну смешнее некуда
think of anything funnier  so that a
придумать чтоб
toilet as it is it is just like well in
а унитаз как он он просто как вот ну в
reality imagine how it is this toilet
реальности представить как он это унита
he will put it in a backpack and
он что будет в рюкзак его положит и с
will
ним будет
walk with it as he  will take it out you need to
ходить как он его вывезет его же надо
take out some toilet I don't know what kind of
вывести какой унитаз Я не знаю какой
genius person came up with the
придумал гениальный челове
neighbors neighbors steal
соседи соседи обворовывают
because otherwise toilet Well there's nowhere to put
потому что по-другому унитаз Ну девать
it You won't ride with it on a tank
его некуда Ты с ним на танке не будешь
what is that Tank and it's all there 17
ездить это что Танк и он весь там 17
toilets on m
унитазов на м
yes honestly pioneer Well  what so so it can
да честно пионерска Ну что так так может
be that the
быть что
neighboring
соседний
yard is
двор это
yes Unscrew the neighbor and
да У соседа отвинтить и к себе его
rattled off the story with the toilets how they
оттарабанил историю с унитазами как
dispersed them still Buryats main Buryats still
разогнали е ещё буряты главно буряты ещё
with the toilet Buryats them there there to Buryatia
с унитазные буряты их там там до Бурятии
You get there for money Well, you
Ты доеха за деньги Ну туда же как-то
have to get there somehow I  I don't even really know
надо доехать Я даже сам толком не знаю
where Buryatia is, but somewhere in the area of Lake
где Бурятия но где-то в районе озера
Baikal. Yes,
Байкал
somewhere there, well, beyond the Urals,
Да там где-то ну за Уралом
in short, and to take a toilet somewhere and
короче и чтоб взять где-то унитаз и
take it beyond the
вести его за
Urals. I don't know. An adult can
Урал Я не знаю Взрослый человек ну умеет
count, well, two times two there.  it's
же считать ну там дважд два там
not
же 16 же не
possible to ram a
получается чтоб тарани с
toilet from Ukraine
унитаз с Украины
Zaural I don't know how you do it
Заурал Я не знаю как это у вас
I understand there's still some
я понимаю ещё там ну какой-нибудь
tablet to take away Well, something
планшет отнять Ну что-нибудь такое
light and
лёгкое
small And what about
маленькое
the toilet, what about
А что унитаз что там
the refrigerators, what about me Well, all this is
ещё холодильники что там я Ну вот это
big, how can I just drag all this away
большое как это всё это утащить просто
How can I take that away  maybe and how do you drag it away
Как отнять то можно а как ты утащит
I didn't know how you
прям я не знал как у вас
do it that this
это заходит что такое
happens Are you on a stream somewhere or
бывает А вы на стриме что ли где-то или
what am I looking at you are looking at another monitor
что я смотрю вы в другой монитор
you are silent
вы молчите
I still don't understand you don't talk about toilets
я ж так и не понял вы про унитазы так и
So why do they steal
не гори Так зачем они воруют
toilets? No one steals them. I'm
унитазы Да никто их и не ворует Я про
talking about how it gets into your head
говорю как у вас это в голову залазит
that you can take a
что их взять
toilet, let alone steal it, they
унитаз даже не то что воровать бесплатно
give it to you for free somewhere in the area of, damn it,
тебе дают его где-нибудь в районе там
Kharkov, and then you
блин Харькова и ты его
take it, the toilet is in the Lake
унитаз район озеро
Baikal area.  how is this even
Байкал как это вообще может
possible I'm surprised you're not laughing
быть Я удивляюсь что вы не смеётесь
or what Well I mean you
или что Ну в смысле у вас это
can
укладывается в
figure out that you can take a toilet somewhere in the Carpathian region
голове что взять унитаз в прикарпатье
and cross it over the Urals how much
где-нибудь и попереч его за Урал сколько
will it
перевозка будет
cost to transport Well  in your opinion Well, say
стоить Ну по-вашему вот Ну скажите
something
что-нибудь
what is this Standup of mine I am the only one
что что у меня за Стендап такой я один
speaking be
говорю
quiet how much will it cost to transport
молчите сколько будет перевозка стоить
a toilet beyond the Urals
вот унитаза за Урал
who told you that they transport them beyond the Urals
кто вам сказал что они их за Урал везут
they transport them to the territory of Russia
они перевозят на территорию России там
they sell everything there clearly they transported
продают всё чётко сразу же перевезли
the toilet right away  no in Ukraine toilets are clean it's
унитаз нет в Украине унитазы чистые это
you who don't
у вас вы их не
wipe them down have you ever bought a used toilet
вытирает бэушный унитаз ты когда-нибудь
in your life are you
покупал в своей жизни Вот
crazy
по с ума сошли в
really no one buys a used toilet
натуре никто не покупает бушный унитаз
wait I saw your blogger this one
ну подожди я видел блогер ваш вот этот
from Kursk showed there is this
из Курска показывал там есть этот
flea market  and the guy is selling 50
блошиный рынок и чувак продаёт 50
toilets used Russian Ukrainian
унитазов бэушные российские украинские
Belarusian I don't know what Kani shows
белорусские Я не знаю что показывает
Every Sunday there is a flea market Well,
Каждое воскресенье там блошиный рынок Ну
there is no
нет
such
такого
thing I saw in Kursk in Kursk for
поку я видел вот в Курске в Курске на
this at the market Yes,
это на базарчик Да бэушные унитазы
men are selling used toilets I also know there
мужики торгуют стоят я тоже знаю у нас в
is one in our city  there was no garage and
городе есть один гараж не есть был и там
some crazy guy was selling there
какой-то сумасшедший продавал
all
вся
the slur already I think look have already seen the videos
слу уже Я думаю смотри уже видели ролики
Yes and already the governor of Kursk region
Да и уже губернатор Курской области
admitted Yes that the Russian army is robbing
признал Да что Российская армия грабит
even the population of Kursk region you understand
даже население Курской области понимаете
Not me videos This is not evidence for me not
Не я ролики Это мне не доказательства не
so governor Khinshtein Yes spoke and
так губернатор Хинштейн Да выступил и
said that we will deal with
сказал что будем разбираться с
this I have not heard or
этим не слыхал не
seen  I don't watch TV,
видал Я у на не смотрит никто телевизор
none of these,
никаких этих э
what's her name, none of Skobeeva, none of this,
как её никаких ни скобеева ни вот это
none of this, nobody watches here.
вот всё это никто здесь не
Well, well, grandmothers. Maybe they
Ну ну бабушки Может быть какие-нибудь
knit some socks and at the same time the TV
там носки вяжут и параллельно Телевизор
works, but for them to sell used
работает но чтобы продавали бэушные
toilets. Yes, my wife leaves the house.  will kick you out
унитазы Да меня жена из дома выгонит
if I'm used and bring a basin
если я бэушный и таз привезу
or will I PPP stop stop How will your wife
или меня ППП стоп стоп Как вас жена
kick you out of the house if you
выгонит из дома если вы сами
live there yourself Well, well, I live there myself Well, I
живёте Ну ну я сам живу Ну у меня же
have a woman Wait, how will you How will your wife
есть женщина Подожди как ва Как вас жена
kick you out of your house If you
выгонит из вашего дома Если вы сами
live there yourself
живёте в
head  In short, I will feel bad How
нём голову Короче мне будет плохо Как
so Stop You don't have a
так Стоп У вас нет
wife take
жены взя у
me probably you have a wife
меня поди жена у вас есть
not with a stamp in the passport no even
не чтоб с печатью в паспорте нету аже у
you don't have a wife Well you live alone in
вас нет жены Ну вы живёте сам в этом
I'm not in this house I'm in an apartment You live in the apartment
доме я не в доме Я в квартире В квартире
yourself
вы сами
yes well you live yourself you
живёте да ну то вы сами живёте вы без
live without a woman yes you may have some
женщины живёте да у вас может какая-то
woman Yes but she can't
есть женщина Да но она не может Вас
throw you out of the apartment break your toilet
выгнать из квартиры разбить вас унитаз
because you don't live  together we are talking about
бо это вы не живёте вместе речь про то
what kind of a deal
что за такой подгон
you have What about your sense of
что вы У вас что с чувством
humor I mean It is impossible to bring it
юмора В смысле Невозможно его принести
anywhere not only that you have your own and yes
никуда не мало того что есть свой а ес
Come on let's be honest
Давай давай по чесноку к тебе не
no woman comes to you you are sitting
приходит никакая Женщина ты сидишь
there by yourself like in this one-room
короче сам там типа в этой однокомнатной
apartment  Well, to
квартире Ну по
be honest No, it's yours It's not
чесноку Нет это ваше Это не сам ещё
some other brownie
какой-то корич
coming Yes, why is brownie going
приходит Да зачем кориш что у меня
somewhere, show me everything, show me what you
куда-то всё покажи покажи что у тебя
have in the apartment, if there is, I will admit that
есть в квартире если есть я допущу что
there is a
есть
woman No, I won't admit it, then you'll
женщина Нет не допущу ты тогда
apologize Yes, come on, show me  I apologize
извинишься Да давай покажи я извинюсь
if there really is I will understand that there is a
если есть действительно я пойму что
woman yes although I honestly
женщина есть да хотя я честно
say be
сказать
Well if those are so it really came to me
бе Ну если те так это прям приспичило
that for all sorts of emergency cases in a
что на всякие аварийные случаи в
box from under a
коробке из-под
phone they are hidden just from a woman and
телефона они спрятаны как раз от женщины
then  what if she finds them for
причём пото что если она их найдёт
me than from a
мне же чем от
used one to you if a woman goes to you And
бэушного тебе если женщина тебя идт А
what is
что
with youth Look there on the shell the production date
е с молодо Посмотри там на оболочке дата
Which
Какая
date is shorter hidden Because if a
дату короче спрятаны Потому что если
woman finds it will be a sign of
женщина найдёт будет признак
betrayal we do not use them
измены мы ими не пользуемся
Well Everyone has different customs
Ну У всех разные обычаи
then you keep it  them Well, I'm such a
держишь тогда его их Ну вот такой я
bad person, here they are, lying there in a
нехороший человек вот они лежат там в
box on the whole That is, you admit
коробочке на вся То есть ты допускаешь
that some other one seems to be in your house
что какая-то другая кажется у тебя дома
Yes, why do you want me to
Да ты зачем хочешь чтобы я давал
testify against myself? I just don't
показания против самого себя-то Я не
understand And you are a cunning Don Juan beetle
пойму только А ты хитрый жук
dun as the
дун как говорят
Chinese say Well, what, cunning or not What, well,
китайцы Ну что хитрый не хитрый Что ну
what, what, me or what And how many of them do you have
ну а что я что ли А сколько у тебя штук
there? I
там
have no idea, well, a box of two
кого Понятия не имею даже ну ящик две
pieces,
штуки
10 Well, I dont know, there are definitely 23
10 Ну не знаю 23 точно
Cool And how long ago did you
есть Прикольно А как давно ты их
replenish your
пополнил
stock? Well, I  I don't think I
запас Ну мне кажется я не
know for a long time I don't use it I and Well
знаю давно я не не пользуюсь я и Ну
how many a month a year two
сколько месяц год два
three I love mine in short Madam Yes Madam you
три Я люблю свою короче Мадам Да Мадам
love and these ones have been lying around I don't know a
любишь а эти сколько лежат уже не знаю
year at least I understood  they need to be updated
год не меньше понял их надо обновлять
Because if it lies for a year, its
Потому что если он год лежит
because of education, but not for me, they
так по образованию но не мне они лежат
just lie there and lie like furniture
просто вот лежат и лежат как мебель
Im not a fan of these disposable pleasures there,
я не любитель этих одноразовых утех там
what kind of things are there at all God forbid I
что какие-то вообще Упаси господ Мне это
dont
вообще не
need this at all I dont even know at all
надо я вообще я вообще даже знать не
I know how they are who threw them at me
знаю как они кто мне их
If it comes to that
подкинул Если на то пошло
threw them at me I'm joking I'm a man Well come on
подкинул шучу я мужик Ну давай как Ну
how Well come on how to laugh Well with
давай как смеяться Ну с
you hundred
тобой ста
for what Well you promised to apologize what
за что ну ты обещал извиниться что
and I'm
де а я
harsh you
те жёстко ты
me Russian this is a sacred
меня русского это святое
matter Here I am
дело Вот я
all my life went
вся всё жизнь пошла под
downhill if while showing that children are
откос если пока показа что дест
you kidding or what I mean And what
ты угораешь что ли В смысле А что там
could
может
be a
быть
souvenir saw in the
сувенир видел в
transition
переходе
from not Show They really inflate inflate it
из не Покажи Они реально надуй надуй его
Yeah mouth still on
Ага ротом ещ на
ka Well here you are
ка Ну вот ты
you are sending Come on letter to my Telegram
ты отправляем Давай пись на мий Telegram
right now axis VN
прям зараз ось ВН
apok  this is very and very important YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through scarg ORV in your ban and there are very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos  I show people sometimes I don't
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational links
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams will give us videos that are also interesting and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we will oblige you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
to keep constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in order to show you about
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube  Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
write ah
пиши ah